Guide to the Paul Rapoport Foundation records, circa 1987-2014.
Rapoport, Paul Foundation records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Paul Rapoport Foundation records, circa 1987-2014.
7803
Paul Rapoport Foundation.
26.5 cubic feet.
Institutional records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of the Foundation including committee minutes and working files, grant contracts and files, various publications, awards and foundation history materials, and DVDs and VHS tapes.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Paul Rapoport (1940-1987) helped to found the New York LGBT Community Center and also Gay Men's Health Crisis, the first community-based AIDS organization in the United States. He also helped to raise funds for SAGE, the Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, and other community organizations in New York City. He died from AIDS-related causes in 1987.
The Paul Rapoport Foundation was created following Paul Rapoport's death in 1987. It awards grants to support LGBT and related community initiatives and organizations. In the face of financial straits brought on by the recession of 2008, the Foundation's leaders decided to spend down the organization's funds in a series of large, multi-year grants through 2014. The Foundation closed in 2015.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of the Foundation.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Paul Rapoport Foundation.; Paul Rapoport Foundation.
Subjects:
Gay liberation movement -- New York (State) -- New York.; Gays -- United States.; Lesbians -- United States.; Bisexuals -- United States.; Transsexuals -- United States.; AIDS (Disease) -- Social aspects -- United States.; AIDS (Disease) -- Social aspects; Bisexuals; Gay liberation movement; Gays; Lesbians; Transsexuals
Places:
New York (State) -- New York; United States
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. History, Awards, Policies, and Procedure Files
Series II. Grant Contracts
Series III. Grant Files
Series IV. Publications
Series V. DVD's and VHS
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Series I. History, Awards, Policies, and Procedure Files (Box 1)
  Many folders contain relating correspondence
  - Attorney Certification (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Paul Rapoport- Benefactor, Memorial programs, 1991, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Rapoport memorial plaque, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Memorial for Jed Mattes, Founding Board president. Joel Ifcher, Founding Board vice president, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Preliminary memoranda, 1982, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Assets, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Post-Agreement miscellany, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Trust Agreement, 1983, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1023 filing, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 501 (c) (3) Determination letter, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Rapoport Foundation history, 2008-2010, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Awards and citations received, 2004, 2010, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Press releases, 1989-1991, 2008-2014 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Spend out press releases, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Board member lists, 2004-2009 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Board executive committee duties, 1987, 1993, 2002-2005 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Board term limits, 1996-2005 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Board Honorariums, 2003-2006, 2009, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Board officer elections, 2003-2012 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Board annual elections, 2006-2015 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Board of Officers nominating committee (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Nominating committee, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - New board member packets, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Prospective board member packets, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Board of Directors candidates, 1992-1998 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Nominating committee candidates, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Board of Directors nominating committee, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Board nominating committee, 2006-2010 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Mission statements, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - By-laws and ethical guidelines, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - By-law revisions, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - By-laws original (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Program committee, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Program committee, 2010-2014 (Box 1, Folder 33-36)
  - Closing event, historical time line, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Closing event, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Send out legacy options, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Executive director reports, 1989-1997 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Working group: New York Committee TA workshop, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Executive director reports, 1998-2014 (Box 1, Folder 41-47)
  - Executive committee, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Annual conference "Spending Up, Spending Down", 2011 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Terminating Grant Relationships "Exiting with Grace", 2011 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Executive Director Reports, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Finance Committee policies and procedures, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Finance Committee, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Finance Committee: Donation of artwork, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Paul Rapoport Memorial Scholar, 1989, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Proposal Review Policy, 1990-1991, 1998-1999, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Guidelines, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Mailing New Glines, Funding Cessation, July, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - New Application Formats, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Proposal Review Process, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Evaluation Criteria for Proposals, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Characteristics and Practices of Effective Organizations, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Spend-Out Application and Guideline, 2009-2012 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Guidelines and Letters of Intent Application (Spend Out), 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Grant Agreement, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Spend-Out Grant Evaluations, 2011-2014 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Personal Committee, 1998, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Staff list, 1987-2015 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Staff Job Descriptions, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Staff Evaluation Process, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Staff Evaluation Tool, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Executive Evaluation Process, 1993, 2003-2007 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Personnel Manual and Older Versions, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Rapoport Fund and New York Community Trust, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Rapoport Foundation miscellaneous correspondence, mainly pertaining to resignations and leaves of absence, 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Board Education Sessions, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Board Meetings, Annual Review, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 22-24)
  - Board Retreat, 1993, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 25-26)
  - Ellen Carton: Retreat Facilitator, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Board Retreat, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Retreat Packet Originals, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Strategic Plan Document, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - One-Year Timeline, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Strategic Plan, Phase I Facilitator, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Strategic Plan Phase II Facilitator: Marta Siberio, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Retreat: Research and Handouts, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Corporate Records: Bylaws, Waivers, Asset Distribution records, etc. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Minutes, 1988-1992 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Minutes, 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Minutes, 1998-2009 (Box 2, Folder 38-39)
  - Minutes, 2009-2012 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Paul Rapoport pillow, MU-1449 (Box 26)
  - St. Vincent's Hospital Compassionate Champion award, December 2, 2008; MU-1450 (Box 27)
  - Paul Rapoport Foundation Courage Award, from the Anti-Violence Project, October 18, 2010; MU-1451 (Box 27)
  - Sol Award, 2007; MU-1452 (Box 27)
- Series II. Grant Contracts
  Many folders also contain correspondence
  - Grant memos, 1987-1989, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Grant contracts, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 2-6)
  - Grant contacts, 1992-1996 (Box 3, Folder 7-10)
  - Grant contracts, 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 11-14)
  - Grant contracts, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 15-17)
  - Grant contracts, 2003-2006 (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
  - Grant contracts, 2006-2011 (Box 4, Folder 4-8)
  - Grant contracts, 2011-2015 (Box 4, Folder 9-13)
  - Board Recommended Grants, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Memos, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Series III. Grant Files
  Many contain correspondence
  - Actor's Fund: AIDS Initiative, 1995-2000 (Box 4, Folder 16-21)
  - Advocates for Children, NY: Queer Youth, Education Advocacy, 2003-2005 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Advocates for Youth: LGBTQ Youth Website, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Advocates for Youth: Website, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - African Ancestral Lesbians United for Societal Change (AALUSC), Inc., 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - AIDS and Adolescents Network, NY: Parent and Youth Initiative, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Aid for AIDS, Inc.: New York Immigrant AIDS Link, 2005-2007 (Box 5, Folder 5-7)
  - AIDS Center of Queens County, LGBTQ Youth, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Alianza Dominica Project Encounter, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Ali Forney Center, 2002-2006, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 10-15)
  - Alpha Workshops, 1996-2006 (Box 5, Folder 16-25)
  - American Civil Liberties Union: Lesbian and Gay Rights Project, 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 26-27, 29)
  - American Civil Liberties Union: One-time-only Grant, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - Amnesty International: Outfront, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Asian American Coalition for Children and Family, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Asian and Pacific Islander Coalition of HIV/AIDS: GOE, Transgender Program, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 5-8)
  - Asian American Writers' Workshop: as fiscal agent for GAPIMNY, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Astraea: Working group, 1995-2002 (Box 6, Folder 10-13)
  - Audre Lorde Project: GOE, Infrastructure Development, 1996-2011 (Box 6, Folder 14-22)
  - AIDS Resource Center (See Bailey House): Health Services, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Bailey House: Recreation program, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 24-28)
  - The Balm in Gilead, Inc, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Biashelp: Safety campaign, 1999-2001 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The Birmingham Group: Valley Mental Health Center, Rainbow's End Project, 2001-2003 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Bronx Lesbian Gay Health Consortium: Healthy and Queer in the Bronx, GOE, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 4-6)
  - Bronx Community Pride Center, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Casa Betsaida, Inc.:GOE, 2005-2007 (Box 7, Folder 8-9)
  - Catholic Charity of Brooklyn and Queens: Casa Betsaida, 2009-2011 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Center for Anti-Violence Education: Brooklyn Women's Martial Arts, 1995-1999 (Box 7, Folder 11-12, 14-16)
  - Center for Anti-Violence Education: Lesbian Health Fair, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Center for Anti-Violence Education: GOE, 2000-2004 (Box 7, Folder 17-19)
  - Center for Anti-Violence Education: LGBT Community Violence Prevention Project, 2007-2009 (Box 7, Folder 20-22)
  - Center for Children and Families: Safespace Lifeskills Program, One-time-only grant, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 23-26)
  - Chinese American Planning Council: Project reach, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Church of St. Luke: St. Luke's AIDS project, 19950 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - CitiWide Harm Reduction Program, Inc.: LGBTQ Program, 2005-2010 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
  - City University of New York: Center for Lesbian and Gay Studies (CLAGS), 1996-2001 (Box 8, Folder 4-11)
  - Community Counseling (CCM): Woman at Risk Program (WAR), 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 12-14)
  - Community Health Action of Staten Island, Inc.: LGBT Mental Health Services, 2007-2010 (Box 8, Folder 15-17)
  - Community Health Project, Inc.: Lesbian Health Fair, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 18-19)
  - Community Health Project, Inc.: GOE, 1995-2004 (Box 8, Folder 21-27)
  - Community Health Project as Fiscal Agent for HIV Forum, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Community Health Project, Inc.: Trans Health Protocols and Data, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 29-30)
  - Community Family Planning Council: Project Life Reach, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Community Healthcare Network, Inc.: Transgender Services Project, 2007-2011 (Box 9, Folder 2-4)
  - Community Research Exchange: Jersey City Connections, TA for PWAHG, 1995- (Box 9, Folder 5-11)
  - Congregational Beth Simchat Torah: Rabbinical Intern/Healing Service, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
  - Connecticut Women's Education and Legal Fund Anti-Violence Project, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Correctional Association of New York: Juvenile Justice Project's LGBT Youth Initiative, 2006-2014 (Box 9, Folder 15-18)
  - Dignity USA: GOE, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - The Door: LGBT Arts Therapy, 2003-2005 (Box 9, Folder 20-21)
  - ECQ Group, Inc., 2006-2009 (Box 9, Folder 22-23)
  - Empire State Pride Agenda Foundation: Health and Human Services, GOE, 1997-2003 (Box 9, Folder 24-28)
  - Empire State Pride Agenda Foundation: Network, Pride in the Family, Health and Human Services, 2002-2006 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
  - Equal Justice Works, 2013-2014 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Services: LGBT Mental Health Services, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Center for Anti Violence Education: Fiscal Agent for FIERCE!, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - FIERCE!: GOE, 2006-2011 (Box 10, Folder 7-9)
  - Forest Hills Community House: SAGE/Queens, LGBT Services, 1996-2005 (Box 10, Folder 10-14)
  - Friends of Green Chimneys: LGBTQ Programming, 2001-2014 (Box 10, Folder 15-19)
  - GLAAD: NY Programming and GOE, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Gay and Lesbian National Hotline: GOE, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 21-22)
  - Gay, Lesbian and Straight Education Network, Inc.: Conference and Internship Program, GOE, Northeast Organizing Project, New York Project, 1996-2004 (Box 10, Folder 23-30)
  - GLSEN: Healing the Hurt conference, 2000-2003 (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
  - Gay Men of African Descent: GOE, administrative assistant, 1995-2006 (Box 11, Folder 4-9)
  - Gay Men's Health Crisis: GOE, Discussion groups, Counseling, 1995-2006 (Box 11, Folder 10-18)
  - GenderPac: Scholarships for Conference, 2001-2003 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - God's Love We Deliver: GOE, 1995-2003 (Box 11, Folder 20-28)
  - Grand Street Settlement: LGBT Youth Initiative, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Greenwich Village Youth Council: New Neutral Zone, 1998-2005 (Box 12, Folder 2-7)
  - Greyston Foundation: GLBT Pathmaker, 2001-2003 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - GRIOT Circle: GOE, Expansion of Services, 2001-2010 (Box 12, Folder 9-14)
  - Harlem United: Outreach, GOE, Workshops, HIV Prevention, Trans Expression, Crystal Meth Intervention, Where the Boys Are, 1995-2012 (Box 12, Folder 15-24)
  - Harm Reduction Coalition: LGBT Training, 2004-2005 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Harm Reduction Coalition: LGBT Training, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Hartley Film Foundation, Inc.: fiscal agent for Halal Films, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Health House: GOE, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Heights Hill Mental Health Service: Rainbow Heights Club, 2003-2006 (Box 13, Folder 4-7)
  - Hetrick-Martin Institute: GOE, One-time-only grant, 1995-2005 (Box 13, Folder 8-16)
  - Hispanic AIDS Forum: Entre Hombres, Transgender Latinas, 1998-2003 (Box 13, Folder 17-21)
  - HIV Law Project: L and G Client Services, GOE, Technical Assistant, One Time Only Grant, 1996-2003 (Box 13, Folder 22-30)
  - Hispanic AIDS Forum: TransLatina Services, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Hispanic AIDS Forum: TransLatina Services, Latino Youth in Actuin, 2005-2011 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - Housing Works, 1995-2001 (Box 14, Folder 3-10)
  - Human Rights Watch: LGBT Public School Students, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Hyacinth Foundation: AIDS Ministry Program, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Identity House: Administrative Coordinator Salary, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - In Our Own voices, Inc.: Unity Through Diversity Health Summit, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Immigration Equality: GOE, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Institute for Gay and Lesbian Strategic Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - International Gay and Lesbian Human Rights Commission: Asylum Project, 1995-2003 (Box 14, Folder 17-24)
  - Institute for Contemporary Therapy: LGBT Affirmative Psychotherapy Program, 2002-2004 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Jersey City Connections: Youth Street Outreach, 2003-2005 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Lambda Legal Defense: GOE, 1995-2004 (Box 14, Folder 27-33)
  - Latino Commission on AIDS(LCOA): Mano a Mano, Por La Vida, GALDE, 1996-2012 (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
  - Latino Gay Men of NY: Program Coordinator, 2002-2004 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Lesbian and Gay Community Service Center: GOE, Talk Sex Forums, Capital Campaign, One Time Only Campaign, Rapaport Youth Leadership Institution, 1995-2005 (Box 15, Folder 6-23)
  - Lesbian and Gay Immigration Rights Taskforce, Inc.: Volunteer Coordinator Salary, Personnel Costs, GOE, 1998-2004 (Box 15, Folder 24-30)
  - Lilith: All in Our Family, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - The Loft: GOE, 1999-2006 (Box 15, Folder 32-35)
  - Long Island Association for AIDS Care, Inc.: Legal Clinic, Hotline Expansion, 1995-1998 (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
  - Long Island Crisis Center: Booklet and Coffeehouse, Pride for Youth, GOE, 1995-2010 (Box 16, Folder 4-17)
  - Long Island Gay and Lesbian Youth, Inc.: GOE, Technical Assistance, 1996-2008 (Box 16, Folder 18-22)
  - Lower East Side Harm Reduction Center: Transgender Mental Health Services, 2007-2009 (Box 16, Folder 23-24)
  - Make the Road by Walking: GL of Bushwick, Globe, 2004-2008 (Box 16, Folder 25-28)
  - Make the Road New York: Safe Communities Initiative, 2011-2014 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Metropolitan Community Church: Personnel Costs, Sylvia's Place, 1999, 2004-2007 (Box 16, Folder 30-33)
  - Minority Task Force on AIDS: HIV Prevention Education, GOE, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - Middle East Natives Testing, Orientation and Referral Services: GOE, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Miracle House: Volunteer Coordinator, Director, 1995-2000 (Box 17, Folder 4-8)
  - Momentum AIDS Project: GOE, 1995-1999 (Box 17, Folder 25-28)
  - Multitasking Systems of New York: GOE, 1995-2003 (Box 17, Folder 15-24)
  - National Association of People with AIDS, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - National Foundation for Jewish Culture, Inc., 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force: Policy Institute, Roundtables, 1995-2002 (Box 17, Folder 31-37)
  - National Latina/o Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Organization, 1999-2001 (Box 17, Folder 38-39)
  - National Lesbian and Gay Journalist Association, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 40-41)
  - National Youth Advocacy Coalition: GOE, 1998-2005 (Box 18, Folder 1-7)
  - New York Academy of Medicine: Info system for WW Web, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - New York AIDS Coalition: GOE, Managed Care Initiative, 1995-2005 (Box 18, Folder 9-15)
  - New York Association Gender Rights Advocacy, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - New York City AIDS Housing Network, 2002-2007 (Box 18, Folder 17-20)
  - New York City Gay and Lesbian Anti-Violence Project: GOE, Bronx Onsite Services, 1995-2005 (Box 18, Folder 21-29)
  - New York Community Trusts: New York City AIDS Fund, 1994-2014 (Box 19, Folder 1-19)
  - New York City Parents of Lesbians and Gay Men, Inc.: GOE, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - New York Legal Assistance Group, Inc.: LGBT Law Project, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - New York Peer AIDS Education Coalition, 1999-2001 (Box 19, Folder 22-23)
  - New York University: Office for LGB Students, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Nonprofit Finance Fund: Operating Reserve Fund Project, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Nonprofit Finance Fund: Ali Forney Center, Apicha, Fierce, NYC anti-violence project, Sylvia Rivera law project, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 26-30)
  - Now Legal Defense, 1996-1998 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Osborne Association: AIDS in Prison Project, 1995-1998 (Box 19, Folder 32-36)
  - PFLAG (Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays) GOE, 2000-2005 (Box 20, Folder 1-4)
  - Park Slope Geriatric Day Ctr, Inc.; LGBT Outreach Coordinator, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - POCC (People of Color in Crisis): Buddy Program, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - People of Color in Crisis: Brothers Network Buddy Program, 1998-2000 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - People of Color in Crisis: Many Men, Many Voices, 1999-2001 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - People of Color in Crisis: T.A. for Bd. Development, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - People of Color in Crisis: Dating 2000, 2001-2003 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - People of Color in Crisis: Pride in the City Testing, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - People of Color in Crisis, Inc.: Pride in the City '05, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - People of Color in Crisis, Inc.: Pride in the City '06, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - People with AIDS Coalition (PWAC) NY G.O.E., 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - People with AIDS Coalition (PWAC) NY: Publication Costs of Newsline and SIDAhora, 1998-2000 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - PWAs Working for Health G.O.E.; D/B/A PWA Health Group, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - PWAs Working for Health G.O.E.; D/B/A PWA Health Group, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - DBA PWA Health Group G.O.E.; DWAs Working for Health, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - PWAs Working for Health G.O.E.; D/B/A PWA Health Group, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Puerto Rican Association for Community Affairs: FA for Pa'Fuera Pa'Lante Conference, 1998-2000 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Queens Lesbian and Gay Community Center: d/b/a Queens Pride House, 2001-2003 (Box 20, Folder 21-22)
  - Queens Lesbian and Gay Community Center: Community Legal Resource Network, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Queens Lesbian and Gay Community Center, Inc. G.O.E., 2009-2011 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Queens Lesbian and Gay Pride Committee: Generation Q Youth Services Program, 2001-2003 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Queers for Economic Justice, Inc.: Shelter Organizing, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Queers for Economic Justice, Inc.: Shelter Organizing Project, 2005-2008 (Box 20, Folder 27-29)
  - Queers for Econ. Justice Inc.: Shelter Organizing Project, 2008, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Reciprocity Foundation, Inc. G.O.E., 2006-2010 (Box 20, Folder 31-32)
  - Research Foundation For Mental Hygiene, Inc.: HIV Center Working It Out Program, 1997-1999 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Research Foundation of CUNY: CLAGS, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Research Foundation State University of NY --- (fiscal agent for) HEAT Program/YMSM and Trans. Health, 2008-2010 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Rightrides for Women's Safety, Inc. G.O.E., 2008-2009 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Safe Horizon Streetwork Project, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Safe Horizon AIDS Peer Educator Program, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Safe Horizon, Inc. Streetwork Peer AIDS Educucation component, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Safe Horizon, Inc. TwistED, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Safe Horizon, Inc.; Streetwork/TwistED, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - St. Luke's-Roosevelt CAYACC Transgender Project, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - St. Vincent's Hospital: TalkSafe, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - St. Vincent's Hospital: Chelsea Village Program, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - St. Vincent's Catholic Med. Ctrs. NY: Immigrant Initiative, 2007-2009 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - St. Vincent's Catholic Med Ctrs.: YMSM Peer Navigator Salary, 2009-2010 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Sanctuary for Families: Lesbian Domestic Violence, 1997-1999 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Seaman's Society for Children and Families: Supportive Service for Men, 1996-1999 (Box 21, Folder 16-17)
  - Seaman's Society for Children and Families: Supportive Services Clinic, 2003-2008 (Box 21, Folder 18-20)
  - Seaman's Society for Children and Families: Supportive Service for Men, 1998-2001 (Box 21, Folder 21-22)
  - Seaman's Society for Children and Families: Supportive Services Clinic, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - SF Project Inform, Inc.: Treatment Action Network, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - SF Project Inform G.O.E., 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 25-26)
  - SF Project Inform G.O.E., 1998-2000 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)